watch-gossip-girl.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Watch Gossip Girl Episodes Streamed Online for Free

**Acceptance of Terms.**  
Please read this policy carefully since by visiting this website (“Website”) and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us.

This website does not collect or distribute any personal information.  
We show ads by valueclick media.  
Please refer below for Valueclick media’s opt out instructions:

Please note that the above link for opt-out Cookies is only applicable to ValueClick Media and not any other ValueClick company website. Also, please note that use of the opt-out Cookies will affect our ability to provide you content and advertisements that will more effectively match your interests and may prevent us from controlling the frequency with which you may view any particular advertisement. Please report any problems related to the opt-out process to [privacy@valueclick.com](mailto:privacy@valueclick.com).  
ValueClick Media also offers “opt-out Cookies” to block the placement of future ValueClick Media Cookies on your system for 10 years from the time you opted out. If you have multiple internet browsers or users on the same computer, you will need to perform the opt-out operation for each browser and/or user. If you or your privacy software deletes the opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to repeat the process.

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “Behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>
